Research and Dean of Graduate Studies, Office of the Vice President for; Records ua400
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative Records, 2001 addition, 1980-2001; 9.4 cubic ft.
  - Christopher D'Elia Correspondence [ 2 of 3 ], 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Christopher D'Elia Correspondence [ 3 of 3 ], 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Department Employee Memorandum and Reviews, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Future Faculty/ Administrator Fellows Program, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Admissions Audit, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Admissions Memoranda, 1993-1997 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action, 1986-1997 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Executive Advisory Council Conference Call, 2001 July 31 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Technology Transfer, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Sponsored Programs Communications Committee (SPCC), 1999 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Y2K Compliance Memorandum and Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Fringe Benefit Rates, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Request from Patty Zeccolo, 1998-2002 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Research Foundation Audit and Allocations, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - ORACLE Implementation, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - OASIS Steering Committee [ 1 of 2 ], 2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - OASIS Steering Committee [ 2 of 2 ], 2000 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Research Advisor Council Conference Call Scripts, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - ORACLE for Doctoral Institutions Folder, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - OASIS Implementation for the Research Foundation, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - RF ORACLE PROJECT (OASIS) Oracle Application Software Implementation Strategy, 1998-2000 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - OASIS Briefing Materials, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - OASIS Presentations, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - OASIS Executive Advisory Council Agendas, 2000 October-2001 June (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Oracle Proposal, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - OASIS Steering Committee and Research Foundation, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Distinguished Service Professor, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Excellence in Research, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - FRAP A, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - FRAP Category A, 1997 April 15-1998 April 14 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - FRAP Category B, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - FRAP B, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - FRAP A, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - FRAP B, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Council on Research, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Council on Research, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Council on Research, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Written, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - University at Albany Foundation Account, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Accounting Procedures, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Articulation Agreements and International Programs, 1984-1990; 0.17 cubic ft.
  This artificial series contains articulation agreements between the University at Albany and international universities.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by institution.
  - Belgrade University Cultural Exchange Agreement, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brazilian Consortium Memorandums of Understanding and Termination, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fundan University Memorandum of Agreement and Addendum, 1979-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Kangwon National University Agreement for Academic Exchange, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Kuwait MBA Program Proposal, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Nanjing University Memorandum of Understanding, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Nankai University Ph.D. Program Memorandum of Understanding, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Republic of Cyprus Memorandum of Agreement, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sofia University Agreement of Cooperation, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Universidad Complutense de Madrid Articulation Agreement, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Universidad del Salvador (Quenes Aires Argentina) Cooperative Agreement, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Universidad Nacional Heredia, Costa Rica Agreement of Cooperation, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - University of Manila Memorandum of Understanding, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - University of Salerno Faculty Exchange Agreement, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Yaound University Agreement of Cooperation, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Yonsei University Agreement of Cooperation, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- V.P. of Research and Dean of Graduate Studies Search Committee Records, 1978-1980; 0.17 cubic ft.
  Administrative History
  After Louis R. Salkever announced that he would retire at the end of the 1978-1979 academic year, a committee chaired by Sociology Professor Dr. Richard H. Hall was appointed to oversee the search for his replacement in early 1978. The Search committee was unsuccessful that year in selecting a long-term replacement and Hall was appointed Acting Vice President for Research and Dean of Graduate Studies, while Dr. Marguerite Q. Warren took over as chair of the Search committee for the next academic year.
  This series contains meeting schedules and minutes of Search Committee meetings, documentation of how the position was advertised, affirmative action data, correspondence between committee members, pamphlets on how to organize a search committee, solicitations of candidate recommendations from other universities and form letters sent to applicants for the position.
  - Search Committee II Personnel, Affirm. Action, Aps, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Search Committee II Membership and Mailing Labels, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - VP/DEAN Search (II), 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - MCST Letters, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Job Description, Selection Criteria and Search Process, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Letter to SUNYA Faculty Members, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Communications From O'Leary, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes of Committee Meetings, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Schedules and Announcements, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Membership of the Search Committee & Mailing Labels, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Search Committee - V.P. for Research, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Search Committee II MCST Letters, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Search Committee II Nominators, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Publications, 1994-2013; 0.17 cubic ft.
  Files in this series have been arranged chronologically.
  This artificial series is made up of publications released by the Office of Research highlighting both faculty and student research, as well as a publication commemorating the University's sesquicentennial in 1994.
  - Sesquicentennial Commemoration, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Research Quarterly Report, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Engagement Brochure, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 2007-2008 Research Report (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2009-2010 Research Report (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 2011-2012 Research Report (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Communication Engagement 2008-2012 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 2012-2013 Research Report (Box 1, Folder 8)